(this["webpackJsonptrivia-react"]=this["webpackJsonptrivia-react"]||[]).push([[0],{25:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(51)},50:function(e,t,a){},51:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(0),s=a.n(n),c=a(22),i=a.n(c),r=function(){var e=(new Date).getFullYear();return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("footer",null,"\xa9 ",e," Oscar Villalta"))},o=function(e){var t=e.title;return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"header"},s.a.createElement("h1",null,t))},u=a(53),l=a(5),h=function(e){var t=e.answers,a=e.handleClick,n=Object(l.shuffle)(t)||[];return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,n.map((function(e){return s.a.createElement(u.a,{key:e.choice,onClick:function(e){return a(e)}},e.choice)})))},m=a(52),f=function(e){var t=e.question;return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement(m.a,null,s.a.createElement("h2",null,t)))},d=a(3),p=a.n(d),w=a(7),g=a(9),v=a(4),k=function e(){var t=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:{};Object(v.a)(this,e),this.choice="",this.status=!1,Object.assign(this,t)},b=function e(){var t=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:{};Object(v.a)(this,e),this.question="",this.answers=[],Object.assign(this,t)},E=a(11),O=[{question:"If a person holds 3 widgets, How many tires can fit in a locker?",answers:[{choice:"Banana",status:!0},{choice:"Dirt",status:!1},{choice:"Umbrella",status:!1},{choice:"Square root of a triangle",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"If a plane is going 300mph, does Puppy like gyros?",answers:[{choice:"James Cameron",status:!0},{choice:"Martian",status:!1},{choice:"Guitar",status:!1},{choice:"Javascript",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"10 times 6 is...",answers:[{choice:"Car",status:!0},{choice:"George Washington",status:!1},{choice:"Perpetual Motion",status:!1},{choice:"Tower of Hanoi",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"The seven dwarfs are part of which highway",answers:[{choice:"Hans Christian Anderson",status:!0},{choice:"Hamster",status:!1},{choice:"17 USD",status:!1},{choice:"Aorta",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Dallas, Massachussets is adjacent to the cellular membrane on which sandwich?",answers:[{choice:"Salacious Crumb",status:!0},{choice:"Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis",status:!1},{choice:"6 of Diamonds",status:!1},{choice:"Twelveteen",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Udo has a grain of salt. There are many wolves in a hectare.  Is rose the color of a prodigy?",answers:[{choice:"Truffles",status:!0},{choice:"Axe Body Spray",status:!1},{choice:"C",status:!1},{choice:"Vincent Van Gogh",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Actor, inanimate carbon rod, stars in which Sci-Fi potato?",answers:[{choice:"Yardstick",status:!0},{choice:"Blue",status:!1},{choice:"February 14th 2008",status:!1},{choice:"Chicago Bulls",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"A crystalline solution of ketchup is also known as...",answers:[{choice:"External Occipital Protubrance",status:!0},{choice:"Edgar Allen Poe",status:!1},{choice:"Horse",status:!1},{choice:"Ceiling Fan",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Where is the tallest amoeba in a walnut located.",answers:[{choice:"Roast Beef Sandwich",status:!0},{choice:"Labor Pains",status:!1},{choice:"Jaundice",status:!1},{choice:"A-10 Thunderbolt",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"During the War of 485, cosmonauts invented which Tetris Game?",answers:[{choice:"Astral Projection",status:!0},{choice:"Lightning and Thunder",status:!1},{choice:"NORAD",status:!1},{choice:"Isildur",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Human Centipedes are most commonly used for this type of degenerative tissue behavior.",answers:[{choice:"10,000 Maniacs",status:!0},{choice:"Speed of Sound",status:!1},{choice:"Array of Objects",status:!1},{choice:"a battery",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Peanut butter and waffled french fries, sometimes, are referred to this type of oil change",answers:[{choice:"The Quickening",status:!0},{choice:"UMDNJ",status:!1},{choice:"United Airlines",status:!1},{choice:"Grover Cleveland",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"}],j=a(24),y=a.n(j),q=new(function(){function e(){Object(v.a)(this,e),this.httpClient=void 0,this.httpClient=y.a.create({baseURL:"https://opentdb.com"})}return Object(E.a)(e,[{key:"get",value:function(){var e=Object(w.a)(p.a.mark((function e(t){return p.a.wrap((function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.abrupt("return",this.httpClient.get(t));case 1:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e,this)})));return function(t){return e.apply(this,arguments)}}()}]),e}()),C=new(function(){function e(){Object(v.a)(this,e)}return Object(E.a)(e,[{key:"get",value:function(){var e=Object(w.a)(p.a.mark((function e(){var t,a;return p.a.wrap((function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.next=2,q.get("/api.php?amount=10");case 2:return t=e.sent,console.log(t),a=O.map((function(e){return new b(e)})),e.abrupt("return",Object(l.shuffle)(a));case 6:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e)})));return function(){return e.apply(this,arguments)}}()}]),e}()),S=function(){var e=function(){var e=Object(n.useState)([new b]),t=Object(g.a)(e,2),a=t[0],s=t[1],c=Object(n.useState)(!1),i=Object(g.a)(c,2),r=i[0],o=i[1],u=Object(n.useState)(0),h=Object(g.a)(u,2),m=h[0],f=h[1],d=Object(n.useState)(""),v=Object(g.a)(d,2),E=v[0],O=v[1],j=a[m].answers,y=Object(l.find)(j,(function(e){return e.status}))||new k;Object(n.useEffect)((function(){m!==a.length-1||o(!1)}),[m,a]);return{gameIsOn:r,currentQuestionId:m,startGame:function(){var e=Object(w.a)(p.a.mark((function e(){var t;return p.a.wrap((function(e){for(;;)switch(e.prev=e.next){case 0:return e.next=2,C.get();case 2:t=e.sent,s(t),f(0),o(!0);case 6:case"end":return e.stop()}}),e)})));return function(){return e.apply(this,arguments)}}(),handleClick:function(e){if(e.currentTarget.textContent===y.choice)return f(m+1),void O("correct");O("that is incorrect")},questions:a,message:E}}(),t=e.currentQuestionId,a=e.handleClick,c=e.gameIsOn,i=e.startGame,r=e.questions,o=e.message,m=r[t];return c?s.a.createElement("div",{className:"game"},s.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-wrapper"},s.a.createElement(f,{question:m.question})),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"text-center pt-1"},s.a.createElement(A,{message:o})),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-wrapper"},s.a.createElement(h,{answers:m.answers,handleClick:a}))):s.a.createElement("div",{className:"game start-page"},s.a.createElement(u.a,{onClick:i},"Start Game"))},A=function(e){var t=e.message;return s.a.createElement(s.a.Fragment,null,s.a.createElement("h3",null,t))},T=function(){return s.a.createElement(S,null)},x=function(){return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},s.a.createElement(o,{title:"Trivia"}),s.a.createElement("div",{className:"main"},s.a.createElement(T,null)),s.a.createElement(r,null))};a(50);i.a.render(s.a.createElement(s.a.StrictMode,null,s.a.createElement(x,null)),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[25,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.e1a7fc0a.chunk.js.map